[
{ 
      "question": "What is the perimeter <br> of a triangle with sides 1, 4, and 5?",
      "correctAnswer": "10",
      "options": [
        "14",
        "12",
        "10",
        "11"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the perimeter <br> of a triangle with sides 8, 9, and 9?",
      "correctAnswer": "26",
      "options": [
        "21",
        "22",
        "28",
        "26"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the perimeter <br> of a triangle with sides 2, 9, and 6?",
      "correctAnswer": "17",
      "options": [
        "18",
        "17",
        "12",
        "20"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the perimeter <br> of a triangle with sides 6, 3, and 6?",
      "correctAnswer": "15",
      "options": [
        "15",
        "14",
        "10",
        "19"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the perimeter <br> of a triangle with sides 2, 4, and 5?",
      "correctAnswer": "11",
      "options": [
        "10",
        "11",
        "7",
        "15"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the perimeter <br> of a triangle with sides 4, 5, and 4?",
      "correctAnswer": "13",
      "options": [
        "13",
        "11",
        "8",
        "16"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the perimeter <br> of a triangle with sides 7, 6, and 3?",
      "correctAnswer": "16",
      "options": [
        "16",
        "12",
        "17",
        "19"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the perimeter <br> of a triangle with sides 4, 2, and 6?",
      "correctAnswer": "12",
      "options": [
        "13",
        "12",
        "14",
        "10"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the perimeter <br> of a triangle with sides 9, 2, and 5?",
      "correctAnswer": "16",
      "options": [
        "16",
        "13",
        "11",
        "14"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the perimeter <br> of a triangle with sides 3, 3, and 3?",
      "correctAnswer": "9",
      "options": [
        "9",
        "11",
        "6",
        "10"
      ]
    }
]